We're on Enoshima now.
Yay!
Wow.
We're the real people in the 100 km history book!
This way, this way!
Yay!
Once again, here's the map.
Our goal is to reach Tokyo Dome.
We are going to run this 100 kilometers divided by 9 people!
Yay!
We're already running a few minutes after this!
Oh my God!
We're running!
Oh no!
Along the beautiful ocean!
I'm going to run along the ocean to pass the baton to everyone!
I'm already fired up, so I'm going to do my best!
Yay!
No matter how late we are, Koyakun is always there to wind us up.
That's for sure.
I took the test in the shortest time possible... 3 minutes.
Here it is.
It's not good to talk like that.
I'd like to pay my respects at the shrine in Enoshima now.
Let's go.
Let's go!
I'll just take the camera, as a professional.
I don't know what's going to happen next.
My legs... they're killing me!
10 kilometers to go!
The goal!
The goal of the day!
Thank you very much!Thank you!
Yay!
10 kilometers from here.
Yeah!
Thank you for watching!
Okay, let's have a spring, please.
Here, here.
Yes, gentlemen. Here we come on the day.
Let's all work together toward the 100 km Tokyo Dome.
We are...
One Love One Heart!
From everyone
I want you to pat me on the back and I will pat you all on the back.
Let's give them a pat on the back.
Please.
Just strong?
Just strong.
Whoo! Okay!
I'm turning red.
I'm starving. This is bad.
One of us is gonna die.
Oh, my God!
Oh, no!
My back is turning red.
Thank you!
Wow! I'm gonna work so hard!
I'm going to work so hard!
I'll do my best for 10 kilos!
Oh no!
Oh, no!
Okay, let's start!
Here we go.
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
I'm trying!I'm trying!
Go for it!
Here we go!
But it's nice, the scenery is nice, and I'm sure I'll still have plenty of time to talk in the beginning.
I think this 100km marathon is a tough project, but through it, I would like One Love One Heart to spread to more people,
I also hope that One Love One Heart will spread to many more people through this project,
I also hope that the nine of us will be able to overcome various ordeals by achieving this goal together.
I hope that we can overcome many challenges by achieving this goal as a group of nine,
I hope to pass on this strong feeling to everyone in Patong.
I always wanted to be the first to run.
I wanted to be the oldest in the group.
I wanted to be the oldest in the group, so I had to be the first.
I'm going to go for it!
I want to go! I said, "I want to go!
This is tough. It's really hard on my legs.
Hang in there!
Go, go, go, go!
I want to go in the ocean with this!
Here you go.
Hold it right there.
Aah!
Ow, ow, ow.
Oh, my God!
I'm so happy!
I don't think you can miss it.
Come on.
Hang in there.
Someday go for it!
Oh!
Ooh.
Who's gonna hang on?
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go
There they go
Walk, walkWalk. Walk.
You can walk.
Come on.
There's a path for you now.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
I'm glad, I get to see the members.
My legs are twice as tired from the sand course than I thought they would be. It's pretty bad.
Thank you very much.
I was so happy, I got to meet everyone.
It was a good feeling, keep up the good work.
Festivals are fast.
Festivals are fast. It'll be soon.
Yeah.
Good job!
Good work!
Hang in there!
Go, go, go, go!
You want me to go now?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm going!
Just give me a little support!
Bye bye!
They're all this way!
Let's go!
We just finished the halfway point.
I don't know if all the members cheered for me or not,
I don't know if they were pressuring me or not,
I'm not sure if they cheered me up or if they pressured me,
I'm just happy to see everyone,
And now the other half of the tour,
I think the other half of the race is going to be a little harder,
I'm sure the other half of the race will be a little tougher, but I'm going to do my best to keep going!
I want us to be a team that people will recognize when they hear the name "One Love One Heart".
I want to be a group that everyone loves because we are One Love One Heart.I want to be a group that everyone loves because we are a group called "One Love One Heart".
Majikero
Don't run to the internet... I know it's hard... but...
I know it's hard not to run to the internet, but I believe that everyone in Love One will make it to the end.
I believe that everyone in Love One can make it to the end, so today, I want to show the unity of Love One.
Is it almost the goal?
My heart is at the goal, but...
How do you feel about it?
Oops!
My feet are killing me.
The fact that I stopped just now...
The strain on my legs
It's a little too much.
It was a mistake.
I'll pass this on to the other members.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I was thinking about the drummer when I thought about what I was thinking about.
I'm not lying, it's true.
Then, in no time at all, we were at this point.
Without the nine of us and our fans, we really can't make it,
I am grateful to everyone who supports us,
I would like to express my gratitude to all the staff, members, and family members who support me on a daily basis,
I would like to achieve the goal of 10 kilometers.
Unexpected hills, sand, but this is life.
Kita! I can't believe it!
Oh no!
I see them all!
I'm gonna cry!
Oh, no!
Hang in there, Haruma! You got it!
I've got you, Hachitaro!
Everyone, go!
Off you go! Good job!
Bye!
Here they come.Here we are.
You're in Shonan now.
It's over!
That's great!
I've been thinking about Love One all day.
Wow, why?
Why did I do it?
My body is hot.
I'm motivated now.
I'm already working hard.
I'll be with you next time.
Look who's working hard.
A little bit, yeah.
I'm glad I could give you some feedback.
And now...
I left the rest to the members who I can rely on.
Now that I know I'm not alone.
I could do my best and I felt like I had to connect with them.
I love you, OneNapoWanHeart!
I have no problem at all.
I guess so.
I'm just not feeling very comfortable yet.
I'm going to do it more comfortably from now on.
I've never been involved in any kind of track and field events in my life.
But now I have a new opportunity to do something new.
I hope to find something new, something different.
I think this 10 km is pretty easy, isn't it? I think.
I'm the oldest girl in the group, and I'm also the oldest boy.
I'm the oldest male right now.
I'm the oldest of the boys now, and the leader of the group wants us to connect with each other.
I hope to be able to connect with them there.
Isn't it coming soon?
Hey! Taishon! Go for it!
You can do it! You can do it!
That's great!Great!
Then walk slowly.
Slowly.
There are more hills than I thought.
Oh, man.
Too much?
You'll do great.
Can I go now?
You're leaving? Are you sure?
I'm going.
Have a good day!
I'll do my best!
Go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Almyrothroy!
Almikey!
Bye-bye.
You're early.
I'm a little tense about the gig.
I'm a little tense.
Uh, I'm a little scared.
I hear it's para-killer.
In my hometown.
In Mie Prefecture.
It's one of the three most beautiful places in the world.
Matsushima in Mie
is in the list.
Matsushima in Mie is on the list.
I'm not very good at the sea.
I'm afraid of it.
The beach is fine.
But the rest...
Aaaaah!
I'm scared.I'm scared.
It's scary.
It's cool. Wow, I'm already proud of my members, I'm so proud of them now.
Even in elementary school, all the girls usually like boys pretty fast.
What kind of boys do you like?
Boys who are fast!
Well, it's all in the legs, isn't it?
There were a lot of bumpy roads.
I've come as far as I can go.
I didn't measure 11 km.
Oh, is this your goal, too?
Wow, that's fast.
Isshin and I have been together for almost 8 or 9 years now,
I hope I can put my heart and soul into this race, and I hope I can do the same for Ys Carnot and for myself.
I have been preparing as much as possible, so my muscles are sore. Yes, I am.
I feel uncomfortable if I don't talk.
Gentle.
Ah, I see it.
Yes! Hang in there, Haruma!
Almost there!
Come on, Haruma! Go, Haruma! Go, Haruma!
Come on!
Go!
I'm going.
Whoo!
Thanks for your hard work!
Good job!
Good work! Good work! Good work!
Oh, no.
Kaito Miyachika, your clothes are soaking wet.
Kaito Matsukura, you're soaking wet.
Kaito Matsukura, that's amazing!
Kaito Miyachika, it was a mountain road.Kaito Miyachika It was a very mountainous road.
Kaito Matsukura Amazing!
Kaito Matsukura, that's great!
Kaito Matsukura, there you are.
You shouldn't underestimate it.
It's scary.
I'm scared.
Who's next after Hishin?
Yes, sir.
Seriously.
I'm in more pain than I thought
It's painful.
Many times
I had a moment to inspire myself.
This is really...
I'm serious.
The dance teacher at Love One
always tells me to push myself.
She always tells me to push myself.
I realized how important that is.
I've realized that once again.
Oh!
Whoo!
Ow!
Ow, ow, ow!
I got it, I got it, I got it!
Yeah!
Thank you for watching!
You two are so tight.
Oh, man! They look so precious!
I want to give it to you.
That's great!That's great!
But we're only halfway there.
That's fast.
It's been a long time.
Halfway... that's not good...
Hang in there!
Go, go, go, go!
Go for it!
I'm really impressed with you.
Guys, seriously, we're really late.
That's totally fine.
You'll never know if you don't try.
Thank you for watching!
I was actually planning to run in the second half.
But, you know, our weak female members...
It's tough to run the most difficult course when the sun is shining.
So, I took over.
Mio Fujisaki!
I'm sure Mio Fujisaki will finish the course with a smile on her face!
I'm very excited, thrilled, and nervous.
I'm very excited and nervous.
Anyway, I hope that this project will not be lost.
I don't want this project to be lost.
That's all I can think about, and I'll do my best.
I'm nervous. I'm looking forward to it.
Don't worry. I can already see it.
Go, go, go.
There it is.
One moment will return.
Oh, no.
I'm nervous.
Okay...
Good luck, Miyuki Mizusaki.
Thank you.Thank you.
Thanks for your hard work.
Aww!
I really want to run 100 kilometers
I hope we can give you a dream that we could do it.
I hope we can give you a dream that we could do it!
It's a little exhilarating.
Time is
It never ends.